Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series MT. Mel Tapley Collection
  - Audio and Visual Media
    - Blackjack, 1996; CD-2023 (Box MT-8)
      1996 album. Penalty Recordings. Part of Press Mailing (MT-4-210).
    - Lord Finesse: The Awakening, 1995; CD-2024 (Box MT-8)
      1995 album. Penalty Recordings. Manufactured and Distributed by Tommy Boy Music, Inc. Part of Press Mailing (MT-4-210).
    - Lord Finesse: Gameplan / Actual Facts, 1996; CD-2025 (Box MT-8)
      1996 album. Penalty Recordings. Manufactured and Distributed by Tommy Boy Music, Inc. Video Tape (V-6878). Part of Press Mailing (MT-4-210).
    - Globalullabies, CD-2029 (Box MT-8)
      Freyda Epstein, Music For Little People & Warner Bros. Records, "An Inspired Collection of Lullabies from Around the World", information on a sheet of paper, album cover, and CD.
    - African Heritage Movie Network King Part 1 of 2, V-6877 (Box MT-8)
    - Lord Finesse, 1996; V-6878 (Box MT-8)
      "Actual Facts" TRT: 4:21, "E.P.K." TRT: 7:00, "Game Plan" TRT: 4:19. Penalty Recordings 1996. CD (CD-2025). Part of Press Mailing (MT-4-210).
    - Nana Soul: Without You, 1996; TR-9883 (Box MT-8)
      1996 album. Press Kit MT-7-33.
    - Bass IS Base: I Cry, 1996; TR-9923 (Box MT-8)
      1996 "Loose Cannon Cassette Single". Island Records, Inc.
    - Mass Order: Maybe One Day, 1992; TR-9924 (Box MT-8)
      1992 Promotional tape. Sony Music Entertainment, Inc. Manufactured by Columbia Records.
    - RAW, TR-9925 (Box MT-8)
      Ready Or Not Records, So What Publishing. Part of Press Mailing (MT-4-229).
    - Kinfolk: Each & Every Day, TR-9926 (Box MT-8)
      Promotional Tape. American Recordings/Wild West Records.
    - Ellen May Shoshoyan: Songs For My Father, 1989; SR-5550, SR-5551 (Box SR)
      1989 LP. New / Ark Records. 2 separate copies.
    - Dr. Alban: No Coke, 1991; SR-5552 (Box SR)
      1991 Promotional LP. Logic Records. Marketed And Distributed by Arista Records, Inc.
    - 2nd II None, 1991; SR-5553 (Box SR)
      1991 Promotional LP. Profile Records, Inc.
    - Brenda K. Starr: If You Could Read My Mind, 1991; SR-5554 (Box SR)
      1991 LP. Sony Music Entertainment, Inc.